Let us through already!
We need to get to Iroha, so stay out of our way!
That's far enough, you traitors!
You're interfering with the liberation of all magical girls!
Surrender now or else!
Tsukuyo, Tsukasa...
M-Mifuyu...
Please stop. Fighting is pointless.
The Magius' plan... failed.
This was wrong from the start.
I'm sorry for all of the horrible things I made you do.
Wait, what? We can't just stop now!
She's right, what do we tell the others?
I'm sorry things got this far...
But we can't hurt anyone else in the name of the Magius.
We have to stop. For everyone's sake.
Williams is full.
Okay.
Iroha, it's you.
Toga!
Gosh, I missed you.
And this whole time, I didn't even realize how much I did.
Like I was trapped in a fog and forgot all about you.
I know, but it's okay.
I remembered you and there's no way I was gonna give up till I saw you again.
How could I forget?
You're like my big sis.
I won't forget you again, ever.
I won't either.
Hello, big sis.
We missed you.
It's been too long.
You remember?
You do?
Yes, I remember.
I wish I could have told you before, Toga, but I couldn't.
By keeping it a secret, it freed you to do things you wouldn't normally have.
Huh?
Take it easy.
Calm down, it's okay.
No, it's not.
I tried to kill you.
You didn't know.
The reason I made a contract was to save you.
But then I tried to kill you.
Why?
It's fine.
See, I'm okay.
Everything's okay now.
To put our plan into action, we needed magical girls.
So we used Embryo Eve to reach out to the ones suffering the most and drew them to us.
Come to Kamehama, where magical girls can be saved from their fate.
No way, that was you guys?
What we didn't expect was that the majority of the girls who made their way to us were much weaker than others.
What?
They brought with them all the fears that were too much for them to bear on their own.
Toga decided the Magyus would save these girls.
She listened to them, sympathized with them.
After a while, she started to change.
Fear, sorrow, anger.
Toga fell down a well of misery and there was no getting out of it.
At some point, it became too much for her and she snapped.
Alone, we're all weak.
But we can be strong if we just hold hands.
Unfortunately, only the ones on the stage could hold hands.
Huh?
The sad truth of it all is that the ones who were afraid
stayed just out of our reach in the wings stewing in their rage.
She's right.
So I turned into their rage.
What are you saying?
The girls who lost hope.
The ones who couldn't protect themselves.
Crushed by fear and falling into despair as their souls became more tainted.
Saving those magical girls is my job.
My priority.
We decided to change how the world specifically worked for us.
To save the girls who couldn't join us on stage.
Whatever it took, we had to make the doppel system work.
For them.
I'm sorry, Roma.
I got you into all this.
I tried to kill you.
It's okay.
You didn't mean it.
Everything you did, you did for me.
I can't be mad at you because you rest your lives to save me.
It's all that we wanted, in the end.
And it's what we wanted too, but...
The things we put you through, and we didn't even know we were doing it.
That's all in the past now.
The important thing is we're together.
And together we're going to fix everything that went wrong.
You think we can?
What's done is done.
All that matters is what we do next.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
All right then.
But if we're going to make things right,
there's something I need to clear up for myself first.
Nemu?
What is it?
You knew everything this whole time, so why didn't you tell me?
I'm sorry, Toka.
I don't want your sorries.
I want to know why you didn't tell me.
When our plan failed,
I extracted Ui's soul and transferred it to Kyubei's body.
But by doing that,
Ui's existence was cut off from this world.
That meant all traces of her disappeared from here.
Everything, including your memories of her.
The same happened to Iroha.
She forgot about us and our friendship with her,
because we were connected to her through Ui.
When I realized what happened,
I almost gave up on everything.
I thought I lost the things in this world that were precious to me.
But there was hope.
Even though you couldn't remember, Ui,
you kept the plan going.
Somehow, you found a righteousness you didn't have before.
You gave the girls hope again.
And me too.
You made me believe the plan wasn't dead.
I see.
You didn't tell me because you were worried.
You thought if I knew the truth about everything that happened,
I'd abandon the plan.
Yes.
So, as long as I didn't remember anything,
it was better for you.
Is that what you thought?
I did.
How could you?
I'm sorry.
But I couldn't let anything get in the way of the plan.
Now that your memories are back and you know the truth,
what do you want to do?
Iroha's visits.
The lunches she'd bring.
Laughing.
Playing.
That hospital room was my whole world.
Mine too.
Those were the happiest, most precious times in my life.
Having those memories back makes me feel like I can do anything.
I know I can.
I feel the same.
We have nothing left to lose now.
I know, Iroha.
She wouldn't just stand by and let someone sacrifice themselves to save her.
Same for Ui.
She wouldn't want that either.
But that's where you and I come in.
We have nothing to lose.
We can make it happen for them.
You were right to keep things secret.
You had no idea what I'd do about the plan once my memory came back.
I was a risk and hiding the truth was the only way to stay on course.
You had no other choice.
I am sorry, Toka.
I hated doing it and I was terrified I was making a mistake.
But thanks to you, I know what must be done.
No matter how wrong we may have been, let's finish the plan so Ui's sacrifice doesn't go to waste.
Hang on.
Go to waste?
What are you guys talking about?
We made a promise with Ui and we're gonna keep it.
Even if it's not exactly what Ui would want.
Agreed.
The two of us will finish what we started.
You gotta be joking.
After everything, you're gonna keep going?
Of course we are.
If we can finish the doppel system, we can change the fates of all magical girls.
But the doppel system doesn't work.
It doesn't save anyone in the end.
Either your doppel takes you over or you turn into a witch.
I'll admit the current doppel system has a few flaws that need correcting.
But once we do that, it should work as intended.
Naturally, there'll be a few sacrifices along the way.
But if that's what it takes to liberate magical girls and end their cycle of despair, we're okay with that.
What are you doing?
When the city's destroyed, that should keep you safe from the shockwave of the blast.
Please don't do this! You can't be okay killing people!
You know this is wrong! It's evil!
You can't talk us out of it. We know what we're doing and why.
We'll take full responsibility.
Listen to me! I know you'd never do something so horrible!
When we're finished and you eventually wake up, all of the horrible stuff will be over.
No, don't! You can't!
We failed once, but there's still a chance to make things right.
Stop ignoring me and listen!
There's still a chance.
We have Ui!
Listen!
Good night, big sis. Hope you sleep well.
Don't do this!
Now then, let's get to work and fix our mistake.
We're gonna keep our promise.
The one we made with Ui when we all became magical girls.
Magical girls have been forced to suffer tragedy and cruelty, but we'll change that story.
The Magius will liberate them and change the horrible ending to a happy one.
Attention, sisters.
The Magius is ready to awaken Embryo Eve and complete the Doppel system.
Once we've deployed the system across the world, magical girls won't have to worry about their souls being taken over by it.
And they will never have to live with the fear of becoming a witch ever again.
It's time for us to come together and make our voices heard.
Join us and cry out with your rage!
No one will say our sacrifice is meaningless.
Our sacrifice is one of pride and purpose!
zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz....
Now what?
That energy blast, it disrupted my emotions.
What's going on now?
I feel so horrible.
We're all suffering.
What's the point?
No matter what I do, nothing's ever gonna be enough.
Hang in there.
Whatever you do, don't summon your doppel.
Why is this happening?
It's Embryo Eve.
They awakened it.
It's that thing?
But we were told it was gonna save us, not hurt us.
The system's malfunctioning, and I'm pretty sure I know why.
There weren't enough witches to power it, which made it go berserk.
This will cause the younger magical girls with unstable souls a lot of pain.
Not to mention these poor girls.
Katie!
Careful!
I couldn't live without Yachiyo.
I'll bury her.
Felicia!
What's the point?
No one cares if I'm alive anyway.
Finally, we are one.
They don't need anyone.
Get each other.
Why is this happening?
The doppels are taking over the girls' souls.
Like Kaede's dead.
Another surprise.
Valpurgisnacht is back on its original course, and heading straight from Itakihara.
It's not too far yet.
Perfect.
We'll head for the city and catch up to her.
Once we do, we'll combine her with Embryo Eve.
Embryo Eve's getting away.
We have to stop it.
What about them?
Go after them.
I can handle these girls.
Hurry up now.
Don't let them get away.
Are you sure?
I'll keep them all safe and protected.
Don't you worry about me.
I'm strong enough.
Alright, I'll go after them.
I know you'll take good care of everyone here, but keep yourself safe too.
Good luck.
Let me feel you.
I know.
Yeah, you look so soft.
I know you'll take good care of everyone's face.
No mikveo is at the house.
I know youδήen.
And you'll be like a boss too.
When you're fast enough, I focus love everyone on the wall.
Just now I'll leave the way you are.
Nothingche.
Liberate the walls.
I know you.
Isada!
Yupo?
Let's.
manuel Kenokaku so we run for now.
This is Jerusalem.
Okay?
Let's leave now.
Mifuyu! Kinect!
Stay away! You'll get caught in it!
Go! Run!
Not a chance! I'm staying! I can help you!
You can't, Momoko!
You need my help, so shut up and let me help!
It's too late for me to ignore what's going on anyway.
Talk to me. What's the plan?
A doppel is the darkness in a magical girl's heart.
Right now, their doppels are trying to take over their souls.
We have to touch their souls and rip them from the doppels.
Awesome.
Then it's just you and me, like the old days.
Right.
Here we go. Hold on tight!
How the? What are you doing here?
Sorry to barge in. We're here to help you.
I'm weak.
I was always ashamed of that.
But it's because I'm weak that I can relate so well to these girls' tainted hearts.
I understand them.
I know all about their worries and fears, and I know I can help them.
No, don't!
If you try to take the darkness from their hearts, it's going to shatter yours!
I could have helped before, but I was too scared.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Tsuruno.
I should have opened up to you way sooner.
I guess this is it, then.
It's time to stop running away and face my fate.
No.
You should go, Mitama.
Once again, you're leaving me out.
It's not that at all.
You need to stay safe.
For them, they'll need someone like you.
She's right.
They're gonna need a good coordinator.
You're forgetting your promise, Momoko.
You said you'd take care of me forever, remember?
I'm sorry.
If there was any other way, I would.
It's okay, I know.
Kaede, what are you doing there?
Can you hear me?
Jump.
I'm here.
Poor Kaede.
You were so scared of losing your home.
And your friends, too.
I was.
I still am.
No matter what happens to you, you'll always have a home with me.
And I know I'll always have one with you.
We're friends, after all.
Yeah, we are.
You too, Momoko.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
For not understanding you sooner.
Hi, Mifuyu.
Hey, wait.
Where are we?
Yes.
I'm scared.
It hurts.
I'm sad.
I'm lonely.
It hurts.
But I'm not alone anymore.
Maybe everything's not okay.
But it's not as bad as it could be.
So let's be friends and move on.
All of us.
Together.
Out of my head.
What happened to us?
I don't know.
I was dreaming and saw Mifuyu.
I did, too.
I was warm and comfy.
Wait, where's Mifuyu?
And Momoko!
Where is everyone?
I don't know.
Momoko.
Why do magical girls have to suffer like this?
Is there no end to it?
What?
I don't remember.
I let him cry all my oldu.
God叫 me to niceness
I don't remember.
to do whatever.
But I remember hervadGHWIC.